<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">

        <template id="compliance_legal_links" name="Legal Pages Links">
            <!-- audit-ignore-view -->
            <div class="mt-5 border-top pt-3">
                <p class="text-muted small">
                    Related:
                    <a href="/privacy" class="me-2">Privacy Policy</a>
                    <a href="/cookie-policy" class="me-2">Cookie Policy</a>
                    <a href="/terms" class="me-2">Terms of Service</a>
                    <a href="/accessibility" class="me-2">Accessibility Statement</a>
                </p>
            </div>
        </template>
        
        <template id="compliance_privacy_policy_template" name="Privacy Policy Template">
            <!-- [@ANCHOR: compliance_privacy_policy_template] -->

            <!-- [@ANCHOR: compliance_legal_pages_rendering] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_presence] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_content] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_ui_tour] -->
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section class="s_text_block pt40 pb40">
                        <div class="container s_allow_columns shadow-sm p-5 bg-white rounded mt-4 mb-4">
                            <h1 class="mb-4 fw-bold">Privacy Policy</h1>
                            <p class="text-muted">Last Updated: January 01, 2026</p>
                            <p class="text-muted">Warning: This is the default
                            version of this document that comes with the
                            software. It was not produced by a lawyer.</p>
                            
                            <h3 class="mt-4">1. Introduction</h3>
                            <p>Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information when you use our community services and user websites.</p>
                            
                            <h3 class="mt-4">2. Data We Collect</h3>
                            <p>We believe in Data Minimization. We only collect what is strictly necessary to operate the platform:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Account Information:</strong> Your name, email address, and login credentials when you register.</li>
                                <li><strong>User-Generated Content:</strong> Any blog posts, website pages, or comments you explicitly choose to publish.</li>
                                <li><strong>System Interactions:</strong> Essential technical data such as standard web server logs necessary for security and abuse prevention.</li>
                            </ul>
                            <p><em>Note: Our platform utilizes privacy-friendly view counters that aggregate page hits without tracking individual IP addresses or relying on invasive marketing cookies.</em></p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">3. How We Use Your Data</h3>
                            <p>We use your data exclusively to provide the services you request, such as rendering your personal website, delivering email digests to which you have explicitly subscribed, and moderating community safety.</p>
                            <p><strong>We do not sell your personal data to third parties.</strong></p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">4. Your Regulatory Rights (GDPR, CCPA, etc.)</h3>
                            <p>Depending on your jurisdiction, you have robust rights regarding your personal data. We have built facilities directly into your user dashboard to exercise these rights immediately:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Data Portability:</strong> You may download a machine-readable JSON copy of all your authored content via the <code>/my/privacy</code> dashboard.</li>
                                <li><strong>Right to Erasure:</strong> You may permanently and instantly delete all your personal content and remove yourself from our directories via the <code>/my/privacy</code> dashboard.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">5. Community Safety &amp; Reporting</h3>
                            <p>To ensure a safe environment, we operate an abuse reporting system. If you report content, your identity and email address are shielded strictly from the content owner to prevent retaliation, and are visible only to platform administrators.</p>

                            <t t-call="compliance.compliance_legal_links"/>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <record id="compliance_page_privacy_policy" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/privacy</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="compliance.compliance_privacy_policy_template"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>


        <template id="compliance_cookie_policy_template" name="Cookie Policy Template">
            <!-- [@ANCHOR: compliance_cookie_policy_template] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_presence] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_content] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_ui_tour] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_views] -->
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section class="s_text_block pt40 pb40">
                        <div class="container s_allow_columns shadow-sm p-5 bg-white rounded mt-4 mb-4">
                            <h1 class="mb-4 fw-bold">Cookie Policy</h1>
                            <p class="text-muted">Last Updated: January 01, 2026</p>
                            <p class="text-muted">Warning: This is the default
                            version of this document that comes with the
                            software. It was not produced by a lawyer.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">1. What Are Cookies?</h3>
                            <p>Cookies are small text files stored on your device when you visit a website. They are widely used to make websites work efficiently and provide a better user experience.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">2. How We Use Cookies</h3>
                            <p>Our platform uses Odoo's native architecture, which prioritizes user privacy. We categorize cookies into two types:</p>
                            
                            <h4 class="mt-3">Essential Cookies (Strictly Necessary)</h4>
                            <p>These cookies are required for the website to function securely and cannot be switched off. They include:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>Session cookies that keep you securely logged in.</li>
                                <li>CSRF (Cross-Site Request Forgery) tokens that protect forms and reports from malicious attacks.</li>
                                <li>Consent memory cookies that remember whether you accepted or declined optional cookies.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h4 class="mt-3">Optional Cookies (Analytics &amp; Third-Party)</h4>
                            <p>We do not load third-party tracking scripts or marketing cookies by default. If optional features are added in the future, our built-in Consent Manager will actively block them until you explicitly click "Accept" on the cookie banner.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">3. Managing Your Preferences</h3>
                            <p>You can manage or withdraw your consent for optional cookies at any time by interacting with the Cookie Consent Manager visible on our website, or by clearing the cookies in your browser settings.</p>

                            <t t-call="compliance.compliance_legal_links"/>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <record id="compliance_page_cookie_policy" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/cookie-policy</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="compliance.compliance_cookie_policy_template"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>


        <template id="compliance_terms_of_service_template" name="Terms of Service Template">
            <!-- [@ANCHOR: compliance_terms_of_service_template] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_presence] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_pages_content] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_ui_tour] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_views] -->
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section class="s_text_block pt40 pb40">
                        <div class="container s_allow_columns shadow-sm p-5 bg-white rounded mt-4 mb-4">
                            <h1 class="mb-4 fw-bold">Terms of Service</h1>
                            <p class="text-muted">Last Updated: January 01, 2026</p>
                            <p class="text-muted">Warning: This is the default
                            version of this document that comes with the
                            software. It was not produced by a lawyer.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">1. Acceptance of Terms</h3>
                            <p>By registering an account and utilizing the User Websites and Knowledge modules, you agree to abide by these Terms of Service and our Community Guidelines.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">2. User-Generated Content &amp; Ownership</h3>
                            <p>You retain ownership of the content you create and publish via your personal or group websites. However, by publishing content on this platform, you grant us a non-exclusive license to host, render, and display that content publicly.</p>
                            
                            <h3 class="mt-4">3. Community Guidelines &amp; Moderation</h3>
                            <p>We strive to maintain a safe, respectful environment. You agree not to publish content that is illegal, abusive, harassing, or spam.</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li><strong>Reporting:</strong> Any user or guest may flag content for violating these guidelines.</li>
                                <li><strong>Three-Strike System:</strong> Verified violations will result in a strike against your account. Accumulating three (3) strikes results in an automatic suspension, immediately unpublishing all of your content.</li>
                                <li><strong>Appeals:</strong> Suspended users have the right to submit a one-time appeal via their account dashboard.</li>
                            </ul>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">4. Open Source Licensing</h3>
                            <p>The software powering this community platform is licensed under the <strong>GNU Affero General Public License v3.0 (AGPL-3.0)</strong>. Contributions, codebase modifications, and technical structures are subject to the terms of this open-source license.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">5. Limitation of Liability</h3>
                            <p>This service is provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. We are not responsible for the user-generated content hosted on personal or group pages, nor are we liable for data loss or service interruptions.</p>

                            <t t-call="compliance.compliance_legal_links"/>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <record id="compliance_page_terms_of_service" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/terms</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="compliance.compliance_terms_of_service_template"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>


        <template id="compliance_accessibility_statement_template" name="Accessibility Statement Template">
            <!-- [@ANCHOR: compliance_accessibility_statement_template] -->

            <!-- Verified by [@ANCHOR: test_compliance_ui_tour] -->
            <t t-call="website.layout">
                <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                    <section class="s_text_block pt40 pb40">
                        <div class="container s_allow_columns shadow-sm p-5 bg-white rounded mt-4 mb-4">
                            <h1 class="mb-4 fw-bold">Accessibility Statement</h1>
                            <p class="text-muted">Last Updated: January 01, 2026</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">1. Our Commitment</h3>
                            <p>We are committed to ensuring digital accessibility for people with disabilities. We are continually improving the user experience for everyone and applying the relevant accessibility standards.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">2. Conformance Status</h3>
                            <p>The Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) defines requirements for designers and developers to improve accessibility for people with disabilities. It defines three levels of conformance: Level A, Level AA, and Level AAA. This platform is partially conformant with WCAG 2.1 level AA.</p>

                            <h3 class="mt-4">3. Feedback</h3>
                            <p>We welcome your feedback on the accessibility of our website. Please let us know if you encounter accessibility barriers:</p>
                            <ul>
                                <li>E-mail: <a t-attf-href="mailto:#{res_company.email}"><t t-out="res_company.email or 'admin@example.com'"/></a></li>
                            </ul>

                            <t t-call="compliance.compliance_legal_links"/>
                        </div>
                    </section>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>

        <record id="compliance_page_accessibility_statement" model="website.page">
            <field name="url">/accessibility</field>
            <field name="is_published">True</field>
            <field name="view_id" ref="compliance.compliance_accessibility_statement_template"/>
            <field name="track">True</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>
